（笛口(ふえぐち)雛実(ひなみ)の息遣い）
（女性）いたっ！
ちょっと気をつけなさいよ！
Whoa! Hey, watch it!
Jeez...
（女性）もう…
（金木(かねき) 研(けん)）あっ…
Hinami-chan!
ヒナミちゃん！
Onii-chan!
お兄ちゃん！
Sorry!
（カネキ）あっ すみません！
Hinami-chan, what's wrong?
ヒナミちゃん　どうしたの？
Mom...
お母さん… お母さんが…
Mom is...
え？　場所は？
Where is she?
Let's hurry!
行こう！
（真戸(まど)呉緒(くれお)）
戦い慣れしていないな…
Quite the inexperienced fighter, aren't you?
You're rather sloppy with the use of your kagune.
せっかくの赫子(かぐね)を
使いこなせていない
A mother sacrificing herself to protect her precious child...
母が子のために命を捨てる…
クク…　虫ずが走る…
滑稽だな
You make my skin crawl.
It's amusing,
watching this little human charade that you ghouls keep up.
貴様ら喰種(グール)が
人間のまね事をしている姿は…
What good will it do if I get involved?
（カネキ）
僕が行ってどうなるっていうんだ…
Amon-kun, you've done enough.
亜門(あもん)君　君はもういい…
あとは私がやる
I'll handle the rest.
What should I do?
どうしたら…
（カネキ）どうしたら…
What should I do?
（笛口リョーコ）ああ… どうして…
イヤよ… そんなの…
Why?
No, it can't be!
It certainly can!
ご名答！
（リョーコ）あ… なた…
Dear...
Good...
いい… いいぞ最高だ
Good! This is great!
Despair, terror, hatred!
絶望 恐怖 憎悪…　その表情だ
Yes, expressions like those!
More! Show me more!
もっとだ　もっと見せろ！
お母さ…　んっ　ん～！
Mom—
ダメだ　静かに
You have to be quiet!
（カネキ）
どうすれば… どうすればいい？
What should I do?
What am I supposed to do!?
I suppose I should listen to your last words out of pity.
せめてもの情けだ
辞世の句でも聞いてやろうか？
What's wrong? There's no need to hold back.
どうした？　遠慮は要らないぞ
おおっと！
Whoops.
What a shame. Time's up.
残念…　時間切れだ
The only thing I could do...
（カネキ）僕にできることは―
この光景を 彼女に
見せないようにするぐらいだった
was cover her eyes from that horrendous sight.
Tell me, oh tell me, the way this world works
ku
ni
Just who is it that exists within me?
In the midst of this broken, broken world
you hollowly laugh without a backward glance
Already broken down, I hold my breath,
furi
izu
frozen
You're vulnerable, unbreakable; irrational, yet sane
a
na
ta
wo
mi
tsu
ke
te
but I still find you
I stand here in this twisted and distorted world
su
ki
to
ot
te
mi
e
na
ku
tte
giving way to a hazy and empty void
Please don't look for me, my hidden self
In this painted world of foreign whims
I never want to see you hurt
o
bo
e
te
bo
ku
no
ko
to
wo
So please don't forget my image
～♪
Huh?
（霧嶋(きりしま)董香(とうか)）あれ？
Um...
あの…
Touka-chan, how are you feeling?
（芳村(よしむら)）トーカちゃん　具合は？
I'm sorry for skipping out on so much work.
すいません
ずいぶん休んじゃって…
It's fine.
（芳村）いや…
Um, did something happen?
あの… 何かあったんですか？
Ghoul investigators have taken Ryouko-san's life.
リョーコさんが
喰種捜査官の手で命を奪われた
リョーコさん…
Ryouko-san...
ヒナミは？
ヒナミは無事なんですか!?
What about Hinami? Is she safe!?
I've put her to sleep in the other room.
（芳村）
今は奥で休ませている
Her face. Did they see her face?
顔は？　顔は見られたんですか？
What is this?
何それ…
最悪じゃないですか…
Could things get any worse?
When the time comes,
（芳村）
ヒナミちゃんは時期が来たら
24区に移そうと思っている
I'm thinking of relocating her to the 24th Ward.
That's a joke, right? That dump of a place?
冗談でしょ　あんなクソ溜めに…
There's no way Hinami can survive on her own in a place like that!
ヒナミ１人で
生きていけるわけないじゃん！
Touka-chan...
トーカちゃん…
白鳩(ハト)を殺せばいいじゃないですか
１人残らず…
We could always just kill the Doves, right?
Every last one of them. I mean, we have Yomo-san,
ヨモさんだっているんだし
みんなで協力すれば…
and if we all work together...
（四方(よも)蓮示(れんじ)）ダメだ…
20区のハトが命を落とせば―
No. If the 20th Ward Doves are killed in action,
then they'll just be replaced. It'll be one after the other.
連中は新たなハトを
次々と送りこんでくるだろう
Until they've hunted all of us down.
（ヨモ）俺たちを狩り尽くすまで
でも…
But—
Touka!
トーカ
Yomo-kun is right.
We must not take any action against them.
ヨモ君の言うとおり
彼らに手を出してはいけない
For the sake of everyone's safety, this is the path we must take.
みんなの安全のためには
それが最善なんだよ
（トーカ）仲間が殺されたのに…
Even though we've lost one of our own?
We've just lost one of our own, and all you think we should do is sit around!?
仲間が殺されたのに
黙って見てるのが最善!?
Hinami's mother was killed.
ヒナミは親を殺されたんですよ？
Wouldn't it be sad if we couldn't avenge her!?
敵(かたき)を取ってあげなきゃ
かわいそうじゃない！
かわいそうなのは
敵を取れないことじゃない
It's not because we can't avenge her that we should feel sad.
The only thing that's sad here...
本当にかわいそうなのは―
is a person who's so blinded by revenge that
they can no longer live properly on their own.
復しゅうに とらわれて
自分の人生を生きられないことだ
What are you trying to imply?
私のことを言ってるんですか？
Back there, if only...
あのとき もしも…
もしも駆けつけたのが僕じゃなくて
トーカちゃんだったら…
If only it was Touka-chan who happened to be there...
You mustn't blame yourself,
自分を責めてはいけないよ
カネキ君
Kaneki-kun.
（カネキ）僕は… 僕は…
I... I...
couldn't do anything at all...
何も… できなかった…
So Jason's base isn't located in the 20th Ward after all.
（亜門鋼太朗(こうたろう)）
やはりジェイソンの拠点は
20区ではなく…
Going by this report, the 11th Ward seems like a better fit.
この報告書から判断するに
11区というのが妥当な線だろうね
例の組織的な動きに
ジェイソンも関与していると？
Do you suspect Jason's involvement in those organized movements?
That's what my instincts are telling me.
（真戸）私の勘ではね
I hate to say it,
悔しいが管轄外では
どうしようもないよ　亜門君
but there's nothing within our jurisdiction to do here, Amon-kun.
We'll hand Jason over to Special Investigator Marude.
ジェイソンは
丸手(まるで)特等に譲るとしよう
The remaining S-rated subjects in the 20th Ward are...
（中島(なかじま)康智(やすのり)）
20区における 残るＳレートは…
大喰(おおぐ)いと美食家(グルメ)ですか
that one binge eater and the Gourmet?
They're both keeping a low profile,
大喰いも美食家も―
almost as if they're adjusting to match our actions.
我々の動きに合わせたかのように
なりを潜めている
In this situation,
こういうときは経験上 追っても
徒労に終わることのほうが多い
I can confidently say that pursuing them would just be a wasted effort.
…となると
Which means...
We go back to the small pickings and catch them up one by one.
地道に足を使って １体ずつ…
We'll definitely reel in a big fish that way.
その先に必ず大物は現れる
必ず…
Without a doubt.
さて 明日からまた
地道な捜査に逆戻りです
All right. From tomorrow onward,
it's back to straight-up detective work for us.
３人とも 今日くらいは
ゆっくり休んでください
That's all for today. Enjoy your evening.
Very well.
分かりました
Yes, sir.
はい
（草場(くさば)一平(いっぺい)）真戸さんは？
And you, Mado-san?
I don't really have much of a life outside my work.
私は仕事以外 能のない人間だよ
Oh, I almost forgot.
Number 745, who is still at large,
７４５番…　我々は顔を
見られていますから―
has seen our faces. As such, be sure to watch yourselves.
くれぐれも気をつけるように
ヘヘヘ…
He's just scaring us. She's only a child after all.
まさか…　相手は子供ですよ
An orphan?
（亜門）孤児か…
So that's them.
（トーカ）あいつらか
Welcome!
（店主）へい らっしゃい！
One shrimp tempura set with chicken rice balls.
えび天セット かしわにぎりで
Again, Nakajima-san?
（草場）またですか 中島さん
うるせえ
Shut it.
He always orders that.
この人 いつもそうなんですよ
I see.
What about you, Amon-san?
亜門さんは？
Large kakiage bowl, order up.
（店主）
かき揚げ大盛り おまちどお
Amon-san, you're from the Academy, right?
（草場）亜門さんは
アカデミー出身なんですよね
Well, yes.
まあ はい
What sort of things did they teach you over there?
アカデミーって
どんなことを学ぶんですか？
喰種に関する法と知識…
Everything you needed to know about ghouls.
They also build on your physical fitness, I suppose.
あとは ひたすら
体を作ってました
It's against regulations, so I can't go into the details.
規則なので
詳しくは お話しできませんが
There are women there too, right?
女性もいるんですよね？
おい 草場
Hey, Kusaba!
同期では２人…
There were two of them in my class.
They were both women of intelligence and strong will.
２人とも聡明で
強い意志を持った女性でした
And?
それで？
Were you interested in either of them?
恋愛とかになったりしたんですか？
That's none of your business!
バカ　いいかげんにしろ！
They were both killed in the line of duty.
２人とも殉職しました
Killed?
（草場）殉職…？
（亜門）ええ
Yes.
S-Sorry, I...
す… すみません　僕…
It's not uncommon.
（亜門）よくあることです
ひたむきな者ほど命を落とす
The passionate ones are always the first to lose their lives.
お先に失礼します
お２人ともお気をつけて
With that, I'll be taking my leave.
You two take care.
Good work today.
お疲れさまです
（草場）お疲れさまです…
アホ
Moron.
M-My bad.
す… すみません
The passionate ones are always the first to lose their lives, huh?
（草場）“ひたむきな者ほど
命を落とす”か…
Then I guess we should kick
back from time to time, right?
頑張るのも ほどほどにしたほうが
いいんですかね？
Don't even think about it.
There's a mountain of work waiting for us.
アホ言うな　仕事は山ほどあるんだ
Not as much as the other wards though.
ほかの区よりは少ないけどな
The guys back at headquarters could easily take care of that stuff for us anyway.
それも本局の人たちが
パパッと解決してくれればいいのに
You say that,
そう言ってるうちは
いつまでたっても支部のヒラだよ
but we're always going to be at the bottom of the employee ladder,
both you and me.
俺もお前も
Amon-san didn't seem to be very interested in moving up, did he?
亜門さんは出世とか
興味なさそうでしたよね
It's as if he motivates himself
purely through a sense of justice.
純粋な正義感だけで動いてる感じで
Yeah. That's just the type of person he is.
ああ そんな感じするなあ
Honestly, he's pretty admirable.
正直 すごいと思いました
There's no point in comparing yourself to someone from headquarters, Kusaba.
（中島）
本局の人間と自分を比べても
しょうがないぞ　草場
Right.
（草場）実は僕
デスクワーク希望だったんですよ
Actually, I was hoping for some desk work.
It's easier and safer.
そっちのほうが楽だし安全だし…
But then, looking at him,
でも 彼を見ていると
こっちまで胸が熱くなるような…
I find myself getting excited as well...
もっと現場で頑張ってみようと…
Maybe I'll try harder at work.
草場？
Kusaba...
Kusaba!
草場ー！
Why, you...
てめえ…
（中島）うう…
（亜門）中島さん！　下がって！
Nakajima-san, stand back!
（亜門）こいつは…
Who is that?
Ukaku!
（亜門）羽赫(うかく)！　瞬発型の喰種か
So you're a high-speed type of ghoul!
This is it...
こんな所で…
いや…
No!
If the foe is before you, even if it costs you your arms and legs...
敵を前にしたら…
手足をもがれても！
（真戸）そうだ 亜門君
That's right, Amon-kun.
それが喰種捜査官というものだ
That's what it is to be a ghoul investigator.
But forgetting to bring your
Quinque is no good, you know?
だが クインケを
忘れちゃダメだろう？
ま… 真戸さん
Mado-san...
You can't afford to lose your composure, Amon-kun.
冷静さを欠いてはいけないな
亜門君
Yes.
はい
Take a short breather.
少し休んでいたまえ
（真戸）ほう
かわしたか 見事見事
Dodged that, did you? Well done indeed.
ん…？　貴様は
昨日殺したメスの喰種の仲間か？
Are you perhaps friends with that female ghoul I killed yesterday?
Would you like me to tell you how that pig was slaughtered?
あのメスブタがどんなふうに
死んだか教えてやろうか？
Oh, my apologies.
ああ すまんすまん
I've completely forgotten. It was just yesterday too.
忘れてしまったよ
昨日のことなのに
She was so weak and miserable...
あまりに弱くて みじめで…
ヘヘヘ…　あれは笑えた
I had quite the laugh.
てめえ…
You bastard...
ちょうどいい　亜門君
This is some great timing, Amon-kun!
Let's go over what you learned at the Academy.
アカデミーで習ったことの
おさらいをしようか
羽赫のグールはスピードに
頼りきった単調な攻撃が特徴だ
A ghoul with an ukaku is characterized by a
flurry of attacks that entirely depend on speed.
（トーカ）やあ！
However, they all share a lack of stamina.
（真戸）
だが 基本的に持久力不足
If you drag out a close confrontation,
the strength of their hits will drop considerably.
短期決戦を逃せば
戦闘能力は著しく下がる
Listen, that female ghoul had a piglet with her, right?
なあ あのメスの喰種
娘を連れていたろう？
Would you mind telling me where she is?
どこにいるのか教えてくれないか？
I mean, I kinda feel bad because she's separated from her mother, you know?
だって かわいそうじゃないか
母親と離ればなれじゃあ
I have to hurry and slaughter her, too.
早いとこ殺してあげないと…
You scum!
（トーカ）てんめえ！
Fool.
バカが…
Do you have any idea how many of your fellow scum I've wiped out?
私がこれまで どれだけのゴミを
葬ってきたと思っている？
You're nothing more than a number!
貴様もそのうちの１匹に過ぎん！
フン　まあいい…
Well, no matter.
Rabbit, the ukaku ghoul...
ラビット　羽赫の喰種か…
Hinami-chan...
（カネキ）ヒナミちゃん…
Touka-chan!
（カネキ）トーカちゃん！
Stay back!
（トーカ）来んな！
（カネキ）でも 血が…
But you're bleeding!
（トーカ）私に構うな…
Don't concern yourself with me.
（芳村）ハトに手を出したか…
（カネキ）えっ？
Did you move against the Doves?
Touka-chan's injured. She needs medical attention.
トーカちゃんケガをしています
手当てしないと…
No.
（芳村）ダメだ
（カネキ）えっ？
Huh?
ダメだと言っている
I said no.
何を言ってるんですか？
What do you mean?
If she's taken her own measures against the Doves,
（芳村）
ハトに手を出したということは―
it means that she's prepared to accept full responsibility for her actions.
すべての責任を１人で
背負う覚悟をしたということ
Whether she lives or dies is of no concern to anyone else.
生きるも死ぬも
他人が関与することではない
You can't be serious!
そんな…
わっ　トーカちゃん！
Touka-chan!
（カネキ）トーカちゃん！
（芳村）よしなさい
Stop this!
Manager, I'm sure you've been through a lot,
きっと 店長は
いろんなことが見えていて
and you have those experiences to back your actions.
その上で
判断されているんだと思います
But when the decision to strike back against the investigators comes,
でも僕には捜査官に手を出すことが
どれほどの覚悟なのかも―
or when the rules of a ghoul's society are concerned,
喰種の世界の掟も
何ひとつ分かりません
I don't understand anything at all.
That's why I need to experience these moments myself
だから 僕はちゃんと自分の目で
見てから どうするか決めます！
before I can decide what's right.
What?
…んだよ？
You need to get bandaged up.
手当てしないと
I don't need it.
要らねえよ
But you're bleeding.
でも 血が…
It has nothing to do with you, does it?
関係ないでしょ あんたに
But still...
でも…
You're annoying the hell out of me!
ちょろちょろ うっとうしいんだよ
人間のくせに！
You're just a human!
I'm half ghoul you know!
喰種も混じってるよ…
（カネキ）どうして１人で…
Why did you go alone?
（トーカ）
私みたいな人殺しが死ぬのはいい
I don't care if a murderer like me dies.
But when a ghoul like Ryouko-san or Hinami
でも…
リョーコさんや
ヒナミみたいな喰種が―
gets killed for no good reason...
一方的に殺されるのは…
我慢できない
I can't stand it.
She knows that what she's doing is wrong.
（カネキ）彼女は分かってるんだ
自分は正しくないって…
She knows, and yet she still fights.
すべて分かった上で
戦っているんだ
Touka-chan,
トーカちゃん
I can't bring myself to kill anyone.
僕には人を殺せない
Even if I think the investigators' goals are unjustified,
捜査官の存在が
間違ってるとも思わないし
I don't believe your actions are the right choice either.
君が正しいとも思わない
But after witnessing Ryouko-san's last moments,
でもリョーコさんの最期を見て
強く思った
I realized that it doesn't matter
whether they're human or ghoul.
人が死ぬのも 喰種が死ぬのも―
If someone close to me died, I'd be heartbroken as well.
僕の知っている人だったら
耐えられない
I'd be devastated if you died, Touka-chan.
僕は…トーカちゃんが
死んじゃったら悲しいよ
That so?
あっそ…
僕にも手伝わせてほしいんだ
I want you to let me help you.
I won't kill any investigators,
捜査官は殺せないけど…
but I refuse to just sit around any longer.
何もできないのは
もう… イヤなんだ
To show our respect for Investigator Kusaba Ippei's bravery,
（幹部）公務中に
喰種の凶行により命を落とした―
a man who lost his life in the line of duty to ghoul aggression,
草場一平捜査官の勇気に
敬意を表し―
a moment of silence.
黙祷(もくとう)！
Is Mado nowhere to be seen?
（丸手 斎(いつき)）真戸は来てないのか？
自分が使ってた兵隊が死んでも
線香もあげに来やがらねえ
One of his own men has died,
and he can't even muster the effort to pay his respects.
上司のかがみだな
That's pretty reflective on him as a superior.
You know, Amon. It'll be the same when you die, too.
おう 亜門
あいつは お前が死んでもこうだぞ
If only that one thing hadn't happened,
あのバカもあんなことがなきゃ―
今頃 准特等ぐらいにゃ
なってたろうに…
that fool would be an assistant special investigator by now.
It's all messed up.
ひんまがっちまいやがって
There's going to be some action over in the 11th Ward soon.
近いうちに11区で動きがある
When that hits, I expect you to help out,
そんときは
てめえらも召集すっから―
so get a move on and clean up the trash in the 20th Ward already.
早いとこ 20区のゴミを片づけとけ
（亜門）中島さん…
Nakajima-san...
亜門さん…
Amon-san...
He was single, fortunately.
あいつが独身でよかった
嫁さんなんかいたら あわれで…
Imagine if he had a wife.
He respected you a great deal.
あいつ 尊敬してたみたいですよ
あなたのこと
What, me?
私など…
Here you go.
（店主）おまちどお
Where's that fellow with the glasses today?
今日は眼鏡のにいちゃんは
一緒じゃないのかい？
A glass of cold water, please.
（中島）
おやっさん　お冷や ちょうだい
へい お冷や３つ…
じゃなくて２つね
All right, water for three— two, I mean.
俺は いつも
このセットを頼むんです
I...
I always order this same set.
That moron Kusaba would chime in every time I ordered,
草場の野郎は
俺が注文するたびに―
"Again, Nakajima-san?" without fail.
“またですか 中島さん”って
うるさくて…
あのバカ
毎回 俺におごらせるくせに…
That freeloader... He'd let me pay for his meal every time,
and I'd only say "Shut up and eat," for God's sake.
黙って食えってんだ　ったく
Who am I going to eat my meals with now, you moron!?
おごる相手が
いなくなっちまったじゃねーかよ
バカ野郎…
There's no good reason for why Kusaba-san was killed!
草場さんが
殺されていい理由なんてない
中島さん　今度
私にも食事をおごってください
Nakajima-san, this time, please pay for my meal!
草場さんより ずっと食いますが！
I can eat a lot more than Kusaba-san ever did!
Well, I guess I can kiss my paycheck goodbye.
給料が飛んじまいそうだな
Touka-chan!
（カネキ）トーカちゃん
これって 今 何やってるの？
What exactly are we doing?
You said you wanted to help me, right?
（トーカ）手伝わせてほしいって
言ったでしょ あんた
Yeah, but...
そうだけど…
This should do.
（トーカ）ここなら…
（トーカ）よし　次行くよ
All right, onto the next.
This time, it's your turn.
（トーカ）今度は あんたの番
（カネキ）何それ？　ちょっと…
待って　トーカちゃん！
What do you mean? Wait, Touka-chan!
INCOMING CALL
SPEAKING
This is Mado.
真戸だ
Senior Investigator Mado,
（女性局員）真戸上等捜査官
we've received some eyewitness accounts regarding number 745.
745番に関しての
目撃情報が入ったのですが
ふむ
They sounded pretty nervous,
so it may have been another prank call,
なんだか声が震えていたので―
よくある いたずら電話かなとも
思ったんですけど 一応お耳に
but I thought you should know.
And?
それで？
No. 745, Shigehara
Elementary School, waterway
I see. Thank you.
ふむ ありがとう
ふむ…
Ghoul Investigator Killed
Men who adhere to a sense of justice...
（亜門）正義を貫こうとした男たち
Children with their loved ones taken away from them...
大切な人を奪われた子供たち
誰かを守ろうと戦った人々
Those who fought to protect someone...
なぜ彼らが
命を落とさねばならない…
Why should they have to lay down their lives?
Shigehara Elementary School
It'd be difficult to use a Quinque there, huh?
（真戸）
クインケが使いにくい場所だな
ふむ
A ghoul's acute sense of smell...
（真戸）喰種特有の嗅覚か…
ラビットは明らかに
745番の縁者だった
The Rabbit was clearly of some relation to number 745.
Shigehara
And now, this...
そして これが…
Shigehara
How do they all connect?
どうつながる？
Come on in. It's ready.
（ウタ）いらっしゃい　出来てるよ
水遊びにつきあってあげよう
ラビット
I'll join you for a little splashing around, Rabbit.
Hinami...
ヒナミ…
I'll change it.
（亜門）変える…
I am going to change...
変えてみせる
間違った―
this backwards...
この世界を
world of ours!
ma
chi
wa
ne
mu
re
do
In this sleepy city
ta
te
mo
no
wa
zu
tto
ke
n
se
tsu
chuu
sa
the buildings get built higher and higher
to
shi
kei
kaku
sui
kou
chuu
under the eye of urban development
ka
mi
a
u
he
bi
It's all a meshwork of snakes
mou
fingu
shi
ta
kan
jou
sen
morphing into a continuous loop
en
doru
fin
a
o
tte
u
ke
yo
Go
en
doru
fin
a
o
tte
u
ke
yo
Go
fueled by endorphins, they go, go, go
yo
ru
no
so
ra
ni
Under the night sky
jou
shou
su
ru
ta
ma
shii
the souls arise
kou
shin
to
kou
wa
jou
ki
wo
is
shi
ta
in erratic parades of morality and faith
ku
i
zu
no
yo
u
da
It's all one impossible quiz
ku
i
zu
no
yo
u
da
It's all one impossible quiz
ma
da
ka
ra
ppo
na
ashi
ta
wa
Tomorrow, the emptiness resumes
ka
gi
ri
na
ku
ro
ni
chi
kai
gurei
in an ever-dulling shade of grey
na
ni
ka
mo
na
re
zu
ni
In the future, the bleakness resumes
ka
gi
ri
na
ku
ro
ni
chi
kai
gurei
in an ever-dulling shade of grey
A
h
ko
n
ya
ki
mi
ga
ho
shii
no
sa
sei
ja
ta
chi
Tonight we will be the saints of your wishes
A
h
o
wa
ri
tsu
ge
te
ho
shii
no
sa
We will be the saints that prophesize the end
sei
ja
ta
chi
Saints
sei
ja
ta
chi
Saints
～♪
sei
ja
ta
chi
Saints
Kaneki-kun! Kaneki-kun!
Oh, Uta-san?
Your mask is done, so I wanted to personally deliver it.
I'm already here anyway, so I'd like to see you put it on.
Please wait one moment...
Yes, just like that. Yes, that's it.
L-Like this?
Good! Very good!
I was thinking of making a one-eyed
mask at first to match your appearance,
but this was definitely the right call!
Thank goodness! It was worth all the effort!
Next Time     "Circular"
Uta-san...